Close

Search for:  Search

Sections
--------

Shows, Podcasts, & Series
-------------------------

Follow Us
---------

Trending Posts
--------------

* [Deny, Defend, Depose: Elites recoil at public support for UnitedHealthcare CEO assassin](https://therealnews.com/deny-defend-depose-unitedhealthcare-ceo-killed)
* ['We are destroying entire worlds': A West Bank rabbi's fight against Israeli Occupation](https://therealnews.com/we-are-destroying-entire-worlds-a-west-bank-rabbis-fight-against-israeli-occupation)
* [‘Everytime we come back, we all get sick’: GA residents affected by September BioLab fire are still going through hell](https://therealnews.com/ga-residents-affected-by-september-biolab-fire-are-still-going-through-hell)
* [Alabama prisoners sued to stop forced labor—a court dismissed their case](https://therealnews.com/alabama-prisoners-sued-to-stop-forced-labor-a-court-dismissed-their-case)
* [Robert Reich predicted the death of the US middle class 30 years ago. We asked him how to save it.](https://therealnews.com/robert-reich-predicted-the-death-of-the-us-middle-class)
* [Assad government falls after nearly 14 years of civil war as rebels seize capital](https://therealnews.com/assad-government-falls-after-nearly-14-years-of-civil-war-as-rebels-seize-capital)
* [Cops cuffed her for failing to signal, but a camera turned their plan upside down](https://therealnews.com/cops-cuffed-her-for-failing-to-signal-but-a-camera-turned-their-plan-upside-down)
* ['Incredibly hypocritical': Hunter Biden's pardon and his father's mass incarceration legacy](https://therealnews.com/incredibly-hypocritical-hunter-bidens-pardon-and-his-fathers-mass-incarceration-legacy)
* [Everything you've heard about this election is wrong. Dr. Richard Wolff explains why.](https://therealnews.com/everything-youve-heard-about-this-election-is-wrong-dr-richard-wolff-explains-why)

Close

Sections
--------

Shows, Podcasts, & Series
-------------------------

Follow Us
---------

Trending Posts
--------------

* [Deny, Defend, Depose: Elites recoil at public support for UnitedHealthcare CEO assassin](https://therealnews.com/deny-defend-depose-unitedhealthcare-ceo-killed)
* ['We are destroying entire worlds': A West Bank rabbi's fight against Israeli Occupation](https://therealnews.com/we-are-destroying-entire-worlds-a-west-bank-rabbis-fight-against-israeli-occupation)
* [‘Everytime we come back, we all get sick’: GA residents affected by September BioLab fire are still going through hell](https://therealnews.com/ga-residents-affected-by-september-biolab-fire-are-still-going-through-hell)
* [Alabama prisoners sued to stop forced labor—a court dismissed their case](https://therealnews.com/alabama-prisoners-sued-to-stop-forced-labor-a-court-dismissed-their-case)
* [Robert Reich predicted the death of the US middle class 30 years ago. We asked him how to save it.](https://therealnews.com/robert-reich-predicted-the-death-of-the-us-middle-class)
* [Assad government falls after nearly 14 years of civil war as rebels seize capital](https://therealnews.com/assad-government-falls-after-nearly-14-years-of-civil-war-as-rebels-seize-capital)
* [Cops cuffed her for failing to signal, but a camera turned their plan upside down](https://therealnews.com/cops-cuffed-her-for-failing-to-signal-but-a-camera-turned-their-plan-upside-down)
* ['Incredibly hypocritical': Hunter Biden's pardon and his father's mass incarceration legacy](https://therealnews.com/incredibly-hypocritical-hunter-bidens-pardon-and-his-fathers-mass-incarceration-legacy)
* [Everything you've heard about this election is wrong. Dr. Richard Wolff explains why.](https://therealnews.com/everything-youve-heard-about-this-election-is-wrong-dr-richard-wolff-explains-why)

Open Search

Search for:  Search

[Donate](https://support.therealnews.com/-/XNTZXPCB) Menu

* Blank (needed for hamburger alignment)

Privacy Policy
==============

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to therealnews.com, and Independent World Television, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Independent World Television, Inc. include therealnews.com and The Real News Network. The Real News Network website is an online news media site. By using The Real News Network website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information if you’re donating to our organization:**

In order to better provide you with a tax receipt and process your donation, The Real News Network may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

* First and Last Name
* Mailing Address
* E-mail Address

If you donate to The Real News Network we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the donation.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you are donating to us or communicating with us. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to your donation.

**Use of your Personal Information**

The Real News Network collects and uses your personal information to process your donation.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

The Real News Network does **not** sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

The Real News Network may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, or provide support. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Real News Network, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The Real News Network may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with the legal process served on The Real News Network or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Real News Network; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Real News Network, or the public.

**Automatically Collected Information**

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by The Real News Network. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of The Real News Network website.

**Use of Cookies**

The Real News Network website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. A cookie helps The Real News Network to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of The Real News Network services or websites you visit.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security of your Personal Information**

The Real News Network secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The Real News Network uses SSL protocol to accomplish this:

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

**Right to Deletion**

Subject to certain exceptions set out below, on receipt of a verifiable request from you, we will:

* Delete your personal information from our records; and
* Direct any service providers to delete your personal information from their records.

Please note that we may not be able to comply with requests to delete your personal information if it is necessary to:

* Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected.
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity;
* Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law;
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act;
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when our deletion of the information is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of such research, provided we have obtained your informed consent;
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us;
* Comply with an existing legal obligation; or
* Otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.

**Children Under Thirteen**

The Real News Network does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**E-mail Communications**

From time to time, The Real News Network may contact you via email for the purpose of providing you with our newsletter, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve when we email you, we may receive a notification when you open an email from The Real News Network or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving emails from The Real News Network, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the unsubscribe button.

**External Data Storage Sites**

We may store your data on servers provided by third-party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

**Changes to this Statement**

The Real News Network reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the website after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

**Contact Information**

The Real News Network welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Real News Network has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Real News Network at:

Independent World Television, Inc.

231 Holliday St.

Baltimore, Maryland 21202

Email Address: contact@therealnews.com

Telephone number: 1(410) 800-4295

TRNN
----

Sections
--------

Shows & Series
--------------

Contact Us
----------

[IWT - The Real News Network  
231 N. Holliday St.  
Baltimore, MD 21202  
USA](https://maps.google.com/maps?z=16&q=iwt%2B-%2Bthe%2Breal%2Bnews%2Bnetwork%2B231%2Bn.%2Bholliday%2Bst.%2Bbaltimore%2C%2Bmd%2B21202%2Busa)

(410) 800-4295

Need to share something sensitive with The Real News?

Use SecureDrop, an anonymity tool for journalists and whistleblowers.

SecureDrop is an anonymity tool for journalists and whistleblowers. You can use our SecureDrop installation to anonymously submit documents to The Real News, and our journalists can use SecureDrop to securely communicate with anonymous contacts.

To protect your anonymity when using SecureDrop, it is essential that you do not use a network or device that can easily be traced back to your real identity. Instead, use public wifi networks and devices you control.

Do NOT access SecureDrop on your employer’s network.  
Do NOT access SecureDrop using your employer’s hardware.  
Do NOT access SecureDrop on your home network.  
DO access SecureDrop on a network not associated with you, like the wifi at a library or cafe.

Once you are connected to a public network at a cafe or library, download and install the desktop version of [Tor Browser](https://www.torproject.org/download/).

Launch Tor Browser. Visit our organization’s unique SecureDrop URL at http://isomzhlu2hqz2ll6t3c7mt67j3mvad2omzptk6cnc2ce2fzdabjjmnid.onion/. Follow the instructions you find on our source page to send us materials and messages.

When you make your first submission, you will receive a unique codename. Memorize it. If you write it down, be sure to destroy the copy as soon as you’ve committed it to memory. Use your codename to sign back in to our source page, check for responses from our journalists, and upload additional materials.

No tool can absolutely guarantee your security or anonymity. The best way to protect your privacy and anonymity as a source is to adhere to best practices.

You can use a separate computer you’ve designated specifically to handle the submission process. Or, you can use an alternate operating system like Tails, which boots from a USB stick and erases your activity at the end of every session.

A file contains valuable [metadata](https://ssd.eff.org/en/module/why-metadata-matters) about its source — when it was created and downloaded, what machine was involved, the machine’s owner, etc. You can scrub metadata from some files prior to submission using the Metadata Anonymization Toolkit featured in Tails.

Your online behavior can be extremely revealing. Regularly monitoring our publication’s social media or website can potentially flag you as a source. Take great care to think about what your online behavior might reveal, and consider using Tor Browser to mitigate such monitoring.

Our organization retains strict access control over our SecureDrop project. A select few journalists within our organization will have access to SecureDrop submissions. We control the servers that store your submissions, so no third party has direct access to the metadata or content of what you send us.

Do not discuss leaking or whistleblowing, even with trusted contacts.

Send us physical mail.

Sending us physical mail is also an option that can preserve your anonymity, especially if you use a public mailbox:

Maximilian Alvarez, Editor in Chief  
The Real News Network  
231 Holliday St.  
Baltimore, MD 21202

Search for:  Search

This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms) apply.

© 2024 The Real News Network [Powered by Newspack](https://newspack.com/) [Privacy Policy](https://therealnews.com/privacy-policy)

Manage Consent

To enhance your experience, we use cookies and similar technologies to optimize how our site works for you. By agreeing, you help us understand your preferences and provide tailored features. If you choose not to accept, some parts of the site might not function as smoothly.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent
